{
    "subject": "resource/WXAF",
    "predicate": "property/city",
    "object": "resource/Charleston,_West_Virginia",
    "human_readable": "WXAF is located in Charleston, West Virginia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8478702902793884,
            "question": "Where is WXAF located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7442736029624939,
            "question": "What state is WXAF in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6450710296630859,
            "question": "Is WXAF in a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6088143587112427,
            "question": "What type of place might WXAF be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6042752861976624,
            "question": "Can you name a nearby landmark to WXAF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6014063954353333,
            "question": "Which city is home to WXAF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3526138663291931,
            "question": "What are some popular attractions in Charleston, West Virginia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30129528045654297,
            "question": "Are there any other businesses or organizations near WXAF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2850435674190521,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Charleston, West Virginia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25965654850006104,
            "question": "What is the population of Charleston, West Virginia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WXAF is located in Charleston, West Virginia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5471_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Charleston, West Virginia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5471_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other businesses or organizations near WXAF?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5471_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular attractions in Charleston, West Virginia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5471_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5471_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that WXAF (channel 14) and WXAF-FM are broadcasting from Charleston, West Virginia. This supports the statement that WXAF is located in Charleston, West Virginia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}